Previously on "Desperate Housewives"
欲乱绝情妻 前情提要
All this time my father has been right across town
我的父亲一直活着
running the feed store?
就在城外经营动物饲料店??
Susan found her real father
Susan找到了她的生父
Ed wants to make the final decision
Ed来做最后的决定
Ed Furarer ,lynette Scoval
lynette met her new boss
lynette见到了她的新老板
I've learned my lesson. Ok, when I get out of here
我已经吸取了教训 当我出去后
Everything's gotta be different
一切都会不同
Carlos promised to change his old ways
Carlos承诺改掉他原来的习惯
Dr. Goldfine has concerns about us being together
Goldfine医生对我们的交往表示担心
and I'm starting to thinking he's right
我想他是对的
While Bree discovered George's true colors
而Bree发现了George的本来面目
George, I don't want to!
George,我不想!
We are engaged! You have to wear it!
我们定婚了! 你必须戴!
I don't think we are any more
我认为我们不再是(订婚)了
Anyone who'd ever been to a party of Bree van de kamp's
去过Bree van de kamp家聚会的人
thought of her as the perfect hostes
都认为她是完美的女主人
Because Bree knew how to take care of her guests
因为Bree知道如何照料她的客人
Her dinners will always served properly
她晚餐准备得又快又好
Her licer always flow freely
她总是不停的给客人倒酒
And her anicdoses were always enjoyable
她总是能取悦她的听众
But on this night,the perfect hostess
但今晚，完美的女主人
was about to find herself...
会发现她自己…
Where's that musiccoming from?
这音乐哪儿来的？
in a very imperfect predicament.
陷入到很不完美的困境中
Uh,I'm not sure.
呃，我不是很肯定
Don't give upon us,baby
别放弃彼此，宝贝
we're still worth one more try
我们还值得再试一次
um,if you'll excuse mefor just one minute.
嗯，请给我一分钟
I know we putour last one by
我知道我们已经忘记过去
just for a rainy evening
在一个下雨的夜晚
george!
george！
I have guests.
我有客人
- What do you thinkyou're doing?
-你以为你在干什么？
We had a tiff.I upset you.
我们小吵了一架，我惹你不高兴
And now I'm just trying to make things right again.
而现在我想弥补过失
It was not a tiff
那不是“小吵一架”
We broke up. It's over.
我们分手了，我们完了
- We can still come through
-我们还是能坚持过去
I am not kidding.
我不是开玩笑
If you do not knock it off,I am gonna call the police.
如果你还不停止，我就叫警察
All right,go ahead.
好吧，请便
I really lost my head last night
昨晚我真的失去了克制
call the police.If they drag me away,
去叫警察，如果他们把我带走
I'm just gonna comeright back here.
我还是会回来的
I want you to hearthe whole medley
我要把整首歌都唱完给你听
Come on!
请听！
Why don't you all take your seats?
请诸位先就座吧
dessert is aboutto be served.
甜点就要上桌了
I really lost my headlast night
昨晚我真的失去了克制
you've got a right
你有权利
to...
来…
yes,bree knew how to take care of her guests,
是的，Bree懂得如何照顾客人
especially those who weren't invited.
特别是对那些不请自来的
-------------------------- www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents --------------------------
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 欲乱绝情妻 第二季第九集
Desperate housewives Season 2 Episode 9
翻 译: 大神一郎，aimar，与世无争 camus，HazelChao，dene，VivienneDew 校 对: VivienneDew  少数派 时间轴: starry
Good guys wear white hats,
好人戴白帽
and bad guys wear black.
坏人戴黑帽
This is how children distinguish
这就是孩子分辨
between good and evil.
好人和坏人的方法
But they soon learn that bad guys
但他们很快就会学到
don't always look so bad.
坏人看上去不一定像坏人的
In fact,sometimes
事实上，有时候
they even seem down right friendly.
坏人们看上去甚至很友善
That is,until you get to know them
他们一向如此，直到
a little bit better.
你了解他们的本质
Hey,fancy seeing you here.
嘿，很高兴在这儿遇到你
I was just out for a little ride.
我刚出来骑会儿车
Don't lie to me,george.
别骗我了，George
You've been riding up and down this street for the last hour.
我知道你在这条路上 来来回回骑了一个钟头
I don't want to do this,bree,
我也不想这样，Bree
but you won't return any of my phone calls.
但你不回我的电话
So stalking me is plan "b"?
所以后备计划就是跟踪我？
Bree,I know I messed up.
Bree，我知道我做错了
I know I got some issues to work on,
我知道我自己 有问题，需要解决
but I'd be willing to see a therapist
但我愿意去看心理医生
if that's what you want.
如果你要我去的话
I'll do anything,but
要我做什么都愿意
how can I show you that I can--
我愿意做任何事来证明…
I can change if you don't give me a second chance?
…我可以改变 请你再给我一次机会
Come on.
求你了
You know I'm not a bad person.
你知道我本质并不坏
I do know that,
我是知道
but I'm just not sure you're a good one,either.
但我也不认为你本质是好人
and we integrated the corporate logo
同时我们把公司的标识
into the jungle background,
整合到丛林背景当中
creating not only an ad for the clothing,
打造出一款不仅仅是 卖衣服的广告
but for the company itself.
同时它也为公司本身作了宣传
I don't get it.
我不明白
What,um,don't you get?
你，嗯，不明白什么地方？
The whole idea just kinda makes my head hurt.
整个构思让我头疼
Is it just me?
是只有我，还是？
No,nuh-unh.
不，不是
You're right. It stinks.
你说得对，这构思糟透了
Sorry,guys. Back to the drawing board.
对不起，伙计们 请重新回到起点
Well,I got tickets to a game.
而我，刚拿到一场球赛的票
Nina,you do whatever you have to do
Nina，你尽你的一切办法
to keep us afloat here.
让我们正常运作
You got it.
悉听遵命
Looks like it's gonna be another late night at the office.
看样子又是个 办公室通宵工作
Nice work,everybody.
干得好，各位
Thank you.
谢谢你们
Could you can the attitude,nina?
你的态度能不缓和一点，Nina？
I'm sorry. What did you just say?
抱歉，你说什么？
You're being rude.
你这样很粗鲁
And it's totally out of line.
而且非常过分
You know how hard we all worked on this.
你知道我们为此埋头苦干
Yeah,I do.
是的，我知道
Nina,I think I speak for everyone here
Nina，我想我说出了 这儿每个人的心声
when I say we are sick and tired of your abuse.
我们都受够了你的虐待
Frankly,you owe us an apology.
坦白的说，你欠我们一个道歉
Is--is this true?
这…这是真的吗？
I mean,I would be mortified
我是说，我会改的
if I thought that I'd hurt any of you.
如果我真的伤害了你们
I mean,If anybody feels like I owe them an apology,
我是说，如果任何人觉得 我欠他一个道歉
please,speak up.
请直说
You? You?
你？你？
You?
还是你？
Gee,lynette.
啊，Lynette
I guess you were mistaken.
我猜你肯定误会了
All right,let's recap,shall we?
好的，我们重新来过，好吗？
Stinky pitch,workin' late,no apologies.
糟透的构思，通宵修改 …没有道歉
Guys!
大家好啊
We talked about this.
我们在讨论这个问题
What happened to standing up for ourselves?
我们在支持自己的时候怎么了
Hot muffins.
热松饼
Any takers?
有人要么
No,stu. These people don't deserve muffins.
不用了stu 这些人不配吃热松饼
hello?
有人么
hello. My name is mark martinez.
你好，我叫 mark martinez
I'm the assistant warden down at fairvew county jail.
我是fairvew 县监狱的副监狱长
Is mrs. Solis available?
Solis夫人在吗？
Uh,yeah,this is her.
恩，当然，我就是
Did somethin' happen with carlos?
carlos出什么事了吗
At 7:43 this morning,
今天早上7：43分
your husband held two guards at gunpoint
你丈夫用枪对着两个狱警
and successfully escaped.
乘机越狱了
He what?!
他什么了！！？
I take it you had no prior knowledge
你事先不知道
he had planned to do this?
他在计划越狱吧
No,of course not.
当然，当然不知道
He's a moron!
他真是个白痴
We have every reason to believe
我们有理由相信
your husband may come to find you.
你丈夫可能会来找你
We believe him to be armed...
他应该持有武器...
and very,very horny.
并且，非常，非常性饥渴
What?
什么？
Surprise,baby.
惊喜，亲爱的
I got paroled early.
我提前假释了
It's so good to see you!
看见你太好了
What happened?
发生什么事了
Well,there's this church group
是这样的，这里有一个教会组织
that helps out catholic prisoners.
帮助信仰基督的囚犯
And they really,really stepped up for me.
他们真的帮了我很大忙
Well,what did they do?
那么，他们做了什么
They lobbied the parole board and it worked.
他们成功的游说了假释委员会
I guess I owe the pope a thank-you note.
我想我欠他们一张谢谢的条子
Less talking,
少谈
more stripping.
多骂
prudy's feed store.
prudy'的饲料店
Apparently,he owns the place.
明显的，他拥有那个地方
How are you gonna do it?
你准备怎么做
What do you mean?
你指什么
I mean,how are you gonna tell him you're his daughter?
我的意思是 你怎么告诉他你是她女儿
Oh,I'm not.
哦，我不会说的
Julie,the man abandoned me before I was born.
Julie，那家伙在我出生前就 把我抛弃了
I don't have a desire to have a relationship with him.
我可不想和他有什么关系
Okay,then I'm really confused
好吧，我真被弄糊涂了
why we're here spying on him.
那我们为什么要监视他
Well,I just wanna see what he's like
是这样，我就想看看他是怎么 样的人
and satisfy my curiosity and
来满足我的好奇心
get it out of my system.
让我不在想这个问题
Well,here you go.
好吧，现在你可以去了
Now you tell charlie that
现在你告诉 charlie
addison prudy says drop in some time.
addison prudy说有时间请来照访
I miss that ugly mug of his around here
那家伙不在这里我还挺想的
I will.
我会的
I bet I know what you're here for.
我打赌我知道你在这干什么
Oh?
是么
You heard about the giveaway.
你听说过礼物么
Well,I got the cowboy hats right here.
实际上，我在这发现了一个牛仔帽
Oh,oh,no,that's okay.
哦，不，太好了
You don't have to give me anything,really.
你不用送我什么的，真的
Relax. This is a promotional item.
放松点，这是改善我们关系的 小东西
Didn't cost me a dime.
没有花多少钱
There you go.
试下
Pretty as a picture.
象副画一样美
I have a dad.
我有个爸爸
He's great!
他很棒
He gave me a hat.
他给了我一顶帽子
That biting thing at the end...
咬来咬去的这招，在最后
Totally blew my mind.
完全把我爽晕了
Please tell me you didn't learn that in prison.
请别告诉我你是在监狱学到的
Yeah.
当然了
Wait. I'm not done with you yet.
等着，我和你还没完
Just give me ten minutes,please.
就给我10分钟，求你了
What is wrong with you?
你怎么了
You are totally useless after sex.
你除了性其他方面真没用
I know. I should probably get my thyroid checked out.
我知道
who's sister mary bernard?
谁是mary bernard妹妹?
those are private.Give me--
这些是隐私，给我--
she's this nun,okay?
她是个修女，可以了吧
She visited me in prisona couple times.
她来监狱看过我几次
She's part of the group that got me early release.
她是那个让我早出狱的组织的成员
Now can I please have them back?
现在我可以要回它们么
"When you walk with godevery day,
当你和上帝度过每一天
"you learn that truth is understood in the mind
你学到用大脑了解真相
but faith burns in the heart"?
但是信仰却在心中燃烧
You don't know what it was like in there.
你不知道在那里面是怎样的.
All right? 20 hours a day,8x10 cell.
明白吗? 每天20小时 8x10大小的牢房
Just you and your mind.
只有你和你的思想
So pretty much just you.
非常适合你啊
It forces you to rexamine everything.
这样你会好好审视一切
I was a very bad person for a very long time,
我很长时间以来都是个坏蛋
but now all that is gonna change
但是现在一切都变了
because I'm on a new path.
因为我走上了一条新的路
A new path?
新的路？
I am going to livea virtuous life.
我要开始过有道德的生活
I wanna do right by you,
我要为你做正确的事
by my mama
为我的妈妈
and by my god.
为了我的上帝
What the hell did they do to you in that prison?
他们在监狱里对你做了些什么啊
All right,this is my last hand,
好吧,最后一把,
and then I gotta go.
然后我就得走了.
Already?
这么早?
I left a proposalon my desk at work.
我桌上还有一份计划书要看.
I have to go over it tonight,or
我必须今天晚上把它看完,否则
you-know-who is gonna have my head.
你知道谁会把我的头给砍下来的.
Nina.
You know,this gainful employment thing
你有没有觉得这个所谓收入不错的工作
is really starting to cut into our social life.
开始干扰我们的社交生活了.
Well,if one of you would just gree to raise my kids,
哼,如果你们中的一位 能答应抚养我的孩子,
I wouldn't need a job.Any takers?
我根本不需要去工作 谁要牌?
- Ha ha.
- 哈哈.
No,I didn't think so.
不，我不要.
Ante up.
加注.
Speaking of child abandonment,
既然说起孩子的事情,
when are you gonna tell your father
什么时候你准备告诉你父亲
that he has a bouncing,middle-aged baby girl?
他有个活泼的，年到中年的女儿?
Soon. I don't wanna ambush him.
快了. 我不想吓坏他.
I'm gonna ease into it.
我准备慢慢的告诉他.
How do you ease into,"hi.I'm your illegitimate daughter"?
怎么慢慢的 说"你好 我是你的私生女"?
Well,actually,there's a "help wanted" sign
嗯,事实上,有一个“招工”的牌子
in the window,so I was thinking about getting a job there.
贴在窗子上,所以我准备 去那里找个工作干.
And you know,he would get to know me,
这样的话,他就能够认识我,
and I'm sure he would like me and I would like him,and...
而且，我肯定他会喜欢我， 我也会喜欢他, 然后...
then one day,he'd say,
有一天,他会说,
"you're like the daughterI never had,"
"你就像个我从未能拥有的女儿一样,"
and I'd say,"well,actually,now that you mention it..."
这是我会说 "嗯,事实上,既然你提到了..."
okay,I'll go first.
好吧,我先说.
That is the most idiotic plan I've ever heard of.
这是我迄今为止听到的最愚蠢的计划.
Why?
为什么?
Because it all hinges on him responding to your personality.
因为这完全取决于他对你这个人的看法.
And let's face it,you are an acquired taste.
而实事求是的来说 你并不是那种人见人爱的类型.
Edie,I am sure susan's father will like her just fine.
Edie,我肯定susan的父亲会喜欢她的.
Thank you.
谢谢你.
I just hope you don't expecttoo much from this relationship.
我只是希望你不要对这种关系期望太高.
I mean,aside from D.N.A.,You might find
我的意思是,除了D.N.A.,你可能会发现
that you don't have that much in common.
你们并无太多相似之处.
I know,but I gotta find outif there's something there.
我懂,但是我确实想看看 我们会不会有一些相似之处.
I've always wanted a dad.
我一直都希望自己有个父亲.
I mean,I know not having oneaffected me.
我是说,并不说来让他影响我.
Well,of course it did.
他绝对会的.
Everyone needsa strong male role model.
每个人都需要有个强有力的男性偶像.
No,they don'T.
不是的,不需要.
I grew up without a father,and it didn't affect me one bit.
我从来就没有父亲 而且对我从来就没有影响.
Edie,how old were you when you lost your virginity?
Edie,你几岁失去处女之身的?
Point well taken.
完全了解了.
Hey.
嘿嘿.
Look what I foundin ed's fridge.
瞧我在ed的冰箱里找到了什么.
hey,stu.
你好,stu.
and nina!
还有 nina!
Hey,lynette,can I see you for a sec?
你好,lynette,我能和你说个事儿吗?
Sure.
当然.
Tsk,tsk,tsk.
Having sex with the support staff--
和下面的员工发生关系--
that's a big no-no.
是绝对不可以的.
Ed's been known to fire peoplefor that sort of thing.
Ed绝对会因为这种事情解雇你的.
lynette,
I know that we've had our little differences.
我知道我们有些小小的分歧.
But at the core,
但是从本质上来说,
I believe that we're both good people,
我相信我们都是好人,
both smart women who are just trying to make it
都是聪明的女人，都想在这个
in this vicious male-dominated jungle--
可恶的以男性为主的社会里获得成功
okay,what do you want?
好吧,你想要什么?
Do you want a raise?
要加薪?
You want a better office?
要换个更漂亮的办公室?
My demands are simple.
我的要求很简单.
I want you to be nicer.
我希望你能够更和善一点.
What?
什么?
No more belittling,
不要轻视,
berating,
不要随意指责,
rude sarcasm.
不要挖苦讽刺.
And in exchange I get your silence?
我换来的是你的沉默?
Yeah. Pretty sweet deal,don't you think?
是的. 你不觉得这是个不错的交易吗?
Um...
嗯...
I'll see what I can do.
我试试看吧.
Great.Okay.
太好了.Okay.
And I'm gonna take your parking space.
还有就是我要你的停车位.
I kid the nina.
我开玩笑的，nina.
you're up early.
你起的太早了.
I'm going to mass.
我要去做弥撒.
- Huh?
- 嗯?
Yeah.
没错.
But it's not even sunday.
但是今天不是星期天啊.
They have mass every day of the week.
他们每天都有弥撒.
Really? When did they start doing that?
是吗? 什么时候开始这样的?
that's sister mary bernard.
那位是mary bernard修女.
Did you see where I put my bible?
你看到我把圣经放哪儿了吗?
So? So she's hot.
那么? 她漂亮.
She's a hot nun.
她是个漂亮的修女.
you cann'tseriously be jealous.
你不会是真的嫉妒了吧.
You mean to tell me that this miraculous conversion of yours
你的意思是说你们之间的 那些不可思议的谈话
has nothing to do with the fact
不是关于那个站在外面女人
that the woman standing outside is a knockout?
有多迷人?
That's what I'm telling you.
就是这个意思.
Um,who are you hereto see?
恩,你来这里找谁?
I'm lynette scavo
我叫lynette scavo
I work here
我在这里工作
Who are you?
你是谁?
Pat. It's my first day.
Pat. 我第一天上班.
Oh. Well,welcome.
嗯. 那好吧,欢迎.
What happened to stu?
stu出了什么事?
You fired stu?
你解雇了Stu?
Oh,lynette,hey.Come on in.
噢,Lynette,进来
I can't believe you would sink so low.
真不敢相信你想掩盖事实
I'm going to ed.
我要告诉ed
Ed knows. This is stu's employee evaluation file right here.
Ed知道了 这是Stu的工作评估报告
This thing is full of black marks.
他的表现不好
Come on,nina. We both know why you got rid of him.
得了吧.我们都知道你为什么想摆脱他
Well,good luck proving it.
那你去找证据吧
Oh,and on a completely unrelated topic,
顺便说个无关的话题
there's going to be another round of firings
下一轮的裁员
coming down the pike.
就要开始了
Ed's been after me to trim the fat.
Ed一直催我解雇多余人员
- You threatening me?
- 你在威胁我?
No,no. Unh-unh.
不,没有
It's just that it's gonna be my job
只是我的工作就是来
to evaluate those who are team players
考量谁是称职的员工
and those who are not.
谁不是
Just a little heads up.
有点过头了?
Just trying to be nice.
试着友好点
I don't know. You seem kinda overqualified.
你看起来有点大才小用啊
Why,'cause I went to college?
因为我上过大学?
No,because you finished high school.
不，因为你高中毕业了
well,I just wanna change my life,and...
我想改变一下生活方式
ever since I was a little girl,
当我还是个小女孩的时候
I've always liked horses and the outdoors,and...
我喜欢马，户外活动
well,I'm just fascinated with...
我着迷于给它们
feed
喂食
Well,I suppose we could give you a try.
我想可以给你机会试试
What?
怎么了?
Something on my nose?
我的鼻子上有东西?
Oh,no. Um,I was just lookingat the color of your eyes.
不是，我在看你眼睛的颜色
You were?
你是?
Yeah.They're just like mine.
是啊，看起来和我的一样
They're--they're nice.
很漂亮
Carol sent you to test me,didn't she?
Carol派你来考验我的,是吧?
What? Who's carol?
什么?谁是carol?
You go back and tell my wife
你回去告诉我老婆
if a private detectivecouldn't fool me,
连私家侦探都骗不了我
well,you're not gonna either.
你也不能
I don't know whatyou're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么
- I just came in to get a little--
- 我只是来应聘
a cute little thing like you
你这样的美女
struts in here,flirts with an old codger like me--
走了进来，对我这个糟老头买弄风情
how dumb do you thinkI am?
你以为我有多傻?
Hey,look at you. Pretty hair.You got a sexy walk.
看看你.一头秀发，走路性感
You got a tight little ass--
还有紧绷的屁股
oh,I'm your daughter.
我是你女儿
What?
什么?
Back in the '60s,you had a brief...
60年代时, 你和一个年轻女人
relationship with a young girl,sophia bremmer.
sophia bremmer有过一段短暂的感情
She got pregnantand had a baby,
她生了个孩子
and that baby was me,
那个孩子是我
which makes you my father.
而你就是我父亲
Hi.
嗨
Mr. Prudy,I'm sorry.
Prudy先生,我很抱歉
I didn't want to spring on you like this.
我本不想让你一下接受的
Where are you going?
你去哪?
You see,when I found out you were alive
当我发现你还活着
and that we both lived in the same city,
而且我们在同个城市
I just wanted to meet you.
我只是想见你
Mr. Prudy?
Prudy先生?
mr. Prudy.
Prudy先生
Hello?
在吗?
hello?
And knock wood,the doctors say I'll keep improving
谢天谢地，医生说我会复原的
slowly but surely.
但会很慢
So how are you?
那你怎么样了?
Good,good.I'm seeing friends,
很好，见见朋友
and I just startedco-chairing a charity event
我要合伙组织
for the junior league,and,um,
青年志愿者组织的慈善活动
and I broke up with george.
而且我和George分手了
Really?
真的?
Dr. Goldfine,do you ever really cure people,
Goldfine医生,你真的治愈过
I mean,even if they're really crazy?
头脑发疯的人吗?
I'm not a big fan of that word.
我不赞同你说的头脑发疯
People either have mental health or they don'T.
有些人没有精神问题 有些有
When they do have a problem,
当他们有问题时
you treat them as if they had any other disease,
你就象治疗其他有疾病的人一样
and sometimes they get better.
有时病情会好转
Well,when I broke up with george,
我和George分手时
I saw something in his eyes.
我在他的眼里看到了什么
It was a kind of malevolence,
狠毒的眼神
and it just didn't seem to me
在我看来
to be the sort of thing that you could cure.
这不是可以医治的
I don't believe in evil either.
我不相信人是邪恶的
We're all just people.
我们是普通人而已
How can you notbelieve in evil?
你怎么能不相信呢?
A man just threw youoff a bridge for no reason.
一个人毫无理由的 把你从桥上丢了下去
Exactly. He didn't know anything about me.
的确，他对我一无所知
He just rode upon his little blue bike
他骑着蓝色的自行车
and tried to hurt me.
想要伤害我
Do I think he's wicked? No. He's disturbed.
我认为他是邪恶的? 不，他被自身的病所困扰
His problems probably stem from a chemical imbalance.
他的问题可能源于化学物质失衡
I believe with enough time and treatment, I could help him.
我相信有足够的时间和治疗 我能治好他
Did you say a blue bike?
你提到了蓝色的自行车?
Black?
黑咖啡?
Great.
好的
I gotta say,lynette,
我要说,lynette
I was surprised to get your call.
接到你的电话我很惊讶
I didn't even think you'd notice I was fired.
我没想到你会注意到我被解雇了
Of course I noticed.You are one of my favorites.
我当然注意到了 你是我最喜欢的人之一
And I thought it was really unfair how it all went down.
对你来说一切都太不公平了
It wasn't that unfair,
这没什么不公平的
I was late all those times
这些天我一直都迟到
and I broke the copier.
我把复印机搞坏了
And I stole all those paper clips.
而且还偷了办公室里的回形针
See,I don't think that's why you got fired.
听着，我想你不是因为这个被炒的
Really?That's what nina said.
真的？这可是Nina说的
Word got out thatyou and nina were...
传言你和Nina...
shagging?
搞在一起？
being intimate.
关系比较暧昧
And nina fired youto keep ed from finding out.
Nina炒了你是防止Ed发现你们俩之间的事
You're kidding.
你在开玩笑吧
And that wasn't rightof her.
她这样做是没理由的
She shouldn't have beenhaving sex with you.
她不该和你发生那种关系
She's upper management.
她可是你的上司
Technically,it's sexual harassment.
确切的说，这是性骚扰
But I was into it.I consented.
可我用了感情的了，我同意了的
Stu,you're A... gofer.
Stu，你是公司打杂的
You can't consent to anything.
你答应了没什么用的
So I think you should talk to ed about getting your job back.
我想你该和Ed谈谈把工作要回来
Why would he care?
他怎么会理这些？
Oh,he'll care.
噢，他会的
He doesn't want you suing him for millions of dollars.
他可不想因为你告他损失几百万
Wow!
哇！
So would nina get in trouble?
那Nina会有麻烦吗？
Well,I'm not gonna lie to you.
这个，跟你说实话吧
There is a possibility she'd get A...
很有可能她
slap on the wrist.
脱不了干系
So...
那么
you'll think about talking to ed?
你会考虑和Ed说找回你工作的事了？
Definitely.
当然
The nurse told meyou were waiting out there.
护士告诉我你一直在外面等着
I just wanted to seeif you were okay.
我只是想看看你怎么样了
Sorry if I spooked you.I've got a bad heart.
很抱歉吓着你了，我心脏有毛病
It's genetic,so you mightwanna get that checked.
这是遗传的，你大概也得要做做检查了
Oh. Okay.
哦，好
Look,don't take this wrong,but I need you to clear out.
瞧，别误会了，但我想你该走了
What? I just got here.
什么？我才刚到这里没多久啊？
My wife is on her way.
我妻子正赶过来
The thing is,if carol finds out
如果她发现
I'e got an adult love childrunning around,
我突然有个已经成年的私生女在周围转悠
that's gonna be the strawthat breaks the camel's back.
会惹得她抓狂的
I mean,it's not exactlythe only time I've strayed.
这种事已经发生不止一次了
Charming.
有魅力
But believe me
不过请相信我
it was niceto finally get to meet you.
能见到你我很高兴
You're a lovely woman.
你是个可爱的女孩
Hon,you really need to leave now.
亲爱的，你现在真的该走了
It's susan.
我叫Susan
My name is susan. And
我的名字是Susan
no,that's not good enough.
不，这不够好
Look,I'M...
瞧，我只是...
I'm trying really hard to be nice about this,
我已经在尽量对你好些了
but you're backing meinto a corner.
可你却一直在逼我
It's not like I want an invitation to thanksgiving.
这并不是我在要求你 请我参加感恩节的家庭聚会
I just wanna have coffee or lunch now and then.
我只是想我们偶尔能够出去 喝喝咖啡或者吃午饭而已
I can't start up something with you.
我不能和你任何瓜葛
It wouldn't be fair to my wife.
这对我的妻子不公平
Oh,that's funny.
哦，这太可笑了
So all the times you were cheating on her,
那你以前对她的欺骗就没关系
that was okay,but having lunch with your daughter--
和你的亲女儿吃午饭...
that just crosses the line.
就越界了
I just want a chanceto get to know you.
我只不过想找个机会了解你
Well,I don't want toknow you.
好吧，我不想了解你
I've already got a family.
我已经有自己的家庭了
Years ago,your mother and icame to an understanding.
几十年前，我和你妈达成一致
I gave her a bunch of money,
我给了她一笔钱
and she agreedto keep things quiet.
她答应我不把这些事抖出来的
Well,I wasn't consulted on that little arrangement.
好，就算这样，可我不在你们的安排之内
I don't think it's fair to punish me for
我想这种惩罚对我来说是不公平的
a mistake I madeyears ago.
就因为一些年前我犯下的一个小错
Is that what you think of me?I'm a mistake?
你就这样看我？我就是个错误?
That's what you need to hear,yeah.
这就是你想要得结果？是的
That's what I think.
那正是我想的
Oh,addy!
哦，Addy！
Addy! Oh!
Addy！哦！
Oh,are you okay?
哦，你还好吗
I'm good,baby.
我很好，亲爱的
The kidsare on their way over.
孩子们正赶过来呢
Hi. I'M... carol.
你好，我是Carol
You are...
你是...
do you wanna tell her,or should I?
你要告诉她吗？还是我说？
I'm your husband'sguardian angel.
我是你丈夫的守护天使
Excuse me?
我不明白？
My name's susan.
我叫Susan
I was buying some horse feed when
我在买马食，那时候
mr. Prudy had an attack behind the counter.I
Prudy先生心脏病突然犯了
gave him C.P.R.,Called 9-1-1.
我给他做了心肺复苏，打了911
Oh! Thank you.
哦！谢谢你了
Thank you.
太感谢了
When I think what--what could have happened...
我还在想这怎么可能呢...
well,I'm gonna get out of here.
好了，我想我该走了
Mr. Prudy,I want you to hurry up
Prudy先生，我要你快点好起来
and get back on your feet.
早点能起来走路
I'm not giving up.
我不会就这样放弃的
I'm gonna be back in the store next week.
下周我还会去店里的
I never got that darn horse feed.
我还没拿到我本该到手的马食呢
I guess I'll puta bag aside for you.
我想我该在你身边放一包马食才好
You do that.
你当然可以这么做
Bree,it's me.
Bree，是我
The police are at my house. They're going through my stuff.
警察在我家里呢，他们在搜查我的东西
What the hell is going on?
TMD怎么回事？
Look,I know you're there.Pick up!
我知道你在.接电话!
Did you have anythingto do with this?
你跟这件事有关系?
Bree? Bree!
George,I know what you did to dr. Goldfine,
George,我知道你对Goldfine医生
and I can see now just how sick you really are,
而且我现在知道你实际上是多么的恶心
so please just turn yourself in,
所以请你坦白吧
and that way you can get the help you really need.
这样你才能得到你需要的帮助
George?
What's going on?
怎么回事？
Oh,I invited sister mary hotpants over for lunch.
我请mary修女来吃午饭
What?
什么？
You said she touchedyour soul,
你说她触摸到了你的灵魂
so I just want to make sure her hands are clean.
所以我只想保证她的手是干净的
so,sister mary,tell me,
那么,mary修女,告诉我,
what's it likemeeting men in prison?
在监狱里会见罪犯的感觉怎样?
Do you bond with all convicts,or was carlos just special?
你是跟所有的罪犯都有关系呢 还是carlos是特殊的?
Well,of course,carlos is special,
当然,carlos是特别的,
but our mission doesa ton of evangelical work with several prisons.
但我们的使命是在好几个监狱开展福音工作
Oh,I get it.
哦,我明白了
Sort of like,today's convictis tomorrow's convert.
就有点象,今天的罪犯,明天的信徒
Something like that,
大约就是这样,
but mostly I do charity work.
但我主要负责慈善工作
Are you two involvedin any charities?
你们俩加入了任何慈善团体吗?
Currently? No.
现在?没有
But we should be.I mean,let's face it,gaby.
但我们会的 我是说 让我们面对它吧,gaby
Buying more stuff isn't gonna make our lives any better.
买再多东西也不能让我们生活得更好
Exactly.
完全正确
Money can't buy happiness.
金钱买不到幸福
Well,sure it can.
当然买得到
That's just a lie we tell poor people
这不过是个撒给穷人听的谎
It's a joke. Lighten up.
开个玩笑. 放轻松.
Can you believe this? I'm married to a woman so selfish,
你能相信吗? 我娶了个这么个自私的女人
she makes fun of the entireconcept of charity.
她竟然嘲笑慈善之举
You are a hypocrite.
你是个伪君子
The money you spentto buy your sports car
你买跑车用的钱
could buy a mud hutfor every peasant in ecuador.
够给厄瓜多尔的每个农民都买栋土屋
Okay,you're right.
好吧,你是对的.
But I'm evolving,starting right now.
但我在努力改变,就从现在开始.
Sister,I would like to donatemy car to your mission.
修女,我愿为了你的使命捐出我的车
What?
什么?
- Carlos,are you sure?
- Carlos,你确定?
Absolutely.
完全确定
Gabrielle and I don't need two cars. We can share one.
Gabrielle和我不需要两辆车 我们能共用一辆
Share? What if you have the car, and I need to go shopping?
共用? 如果你在用车,我要去购物怎么办?
We're gonna cut back on shopping,too.
我们也要减少购物量
Okay,I think we should all just calm down a little bit.
我想我们都该冷静一点
I'm gonna get you that pink slipright now.
我现在就给你车主证
- Carlos...
we're doing this.
就这么办了
I have to--ahem.Uh,here have some of this.
我得--恩 来点这个
No one needs to know.
没人会知道的
Don't even bother. You're not talking me out of this.
别费唇舌了 你不能说服我的
I'm not here to talk you out of anything.
我不是来说服你的
Check in this drawer.
看这个抽屉
Carlos,I wanna apologize for the way I've been acting.
Carlos,我要为我的行为道歉
I mean,here you are trying to turn your life around,
我是说,你正在努力扭转你的生命
and all I can think about are my stupid jealousy issues.
我所想到却只是我愚蠢的妒忌
Yeah,well,let's just get back down there.
是啊,我们回去吧
No,I mean it.I'm sorry.
不,真的。我很抱歉
I wanna be a better person,too.
我也想做个更好的人
I'm sick of being bad.
我已厌倦了做坏人
Forgive me?
原谅我吗?
You're not a bad person.
你不是个坏人
Really?
真的?
No,of course not.
不,当然不是
That's so sweet.
你真好.
I feel so close to youright now.
现在我感觉如此贴近你
gaby.
gabby.
I'm sorry.Guess i am bad.
抱歉 看来我的确我坏
Look,we got a nun downstairs.
我们楼下有个修女
She can wait five minutes.We're giving her a car.
她能等五分钟 我们就要给她一辆车了
Hey,pat,what's going on?
嘿,pat,怎么样了?
I'm not sure.
我不确定
Ed keeps calling people into his office.
Ed不停叫人去他的办公室
I think people are getting fired.
我想大家都要被炒了
Lynette.
Lynette
Yeah.
是的
Lynette...
nina's out. You're in.
nina出局了 你赢了
You areour new V.P. Of accounts.
你是我们的新财务副总经理
I... am?
我?
I just gave her the ax,
我刚把她砍了
along with a bunch of other people.
连着一大堆人
Why? What happened?
为什么? 发生了什么?
He did what?
他做了什么?
He fired a fancy lawyer whothreatened to go to the press.
他聘请了一位律师 威胁要见报
I had no choicebut to pay him off.
我除了付钱没别的选择
He had a video of himand nina together.
他有一卷他和Nina在一起的录象带
Okay. I... get nina,but
好的 我明白nina的事了 但是...
why are you firingeverybody else?
为何你人人都炒?
Stu's taking us to the cleaners.
Stu把我们逼成了洗衣店
If I don't cut backon staff,
如果我不裁员
the next roundof paychecks are gonna bounce.
下一次付给你们的支票就要被银行跳票了
Oh,god,ed.I am so sorry.
哦,天啊,Ed.我真抱歉
Well,it's not your fault.We'll get through this.
不是你的错 我们会渡过这风波的
You and me together.
你和我一起
Oh,can you run down to the art department?
噢,你能去一下艺术部吗?
Someone's gotta can jeff and elizabeth.
要炒jeff和elizabeth的鱿鱼
Yeah. Sure. I'm gonna goand take care of that.
好 当然 我会处理好的
Hey. Congratulations.
嘿 恭喜
This...is not what I wanted.
这...不是我所想要的
I just wanted youto be nicer.
我本意是想让你对我态度好点
You know what?I used to be nice.but
知道吗？我原来是很和蔼的
our boss--I'm sorry. Your boss...
但是，我们的上司，哦，说错了
is incompetent and selfish
是你的上司，他没能力又很自私
and has the attention spanof a poodle.
只注意鸡毛蒜皮的事
I mean,from day one, I have been the only one around here
我是说，从第一天起
keeping this placefrom crumbling down
我是这里唯一在支撑这个鬼地方的人
around his stupid ears.
可他那么蠢，
Oh,nina,come on.
不要这样，Nina
This is the truth here.
我说的是实话
Nice is a luxury that I gave up
优秀是种奢侈的东西，我放弃了
along with vacations and relationships
放弃了假期，好朋友，
and eating at home.
没法在家里吃饭
This job sucks you dry.
这个工作把你都榨干了
So you better kiss those four little kiddies of yours good-bye
所以你最好向你的四个宝贝告别吧
because you have just adopted
因为你要去养
the neediest little childin the world.
另外一个最要紧的小子
Here.
给你
You're gonna need this more than I do.
你比我更需要这个
Hi.
你好
Carlos will be down in a little while.
Carlos 呆会就下来
We had an intense talk.
我们刚才“谈”得很激烈
He's resting.
他在休息
Yeah,I overheard some of your... talk.
我知道，刚才无意中听到你们的... 交谈
Sorry. He's such an animal
不好意思，他真是头“猛兽”
but since we have a couple of minutes,
那既然我们有点时间
why don't we,uh,chat?
我们聊一会吧？
Look,I don't meanany disrespect.
请相信，我无意冒犯
It's just,now that carlos is home,
只是，现在Carlos 在家了
we need to get backon our routine,
我们需要做自己夫妻的私事
and we can't do that if he keeps running off to church
可如果他老是跑去教堂或是卖场，
and charity bake sales.
我们就不能做了
We need "us" time.Do you know what I mean?
我们需要自己的时间。你明白了吗？
I do.
我知道
Oh,good. Good.
那就好
So it would really help our marriage
你若是能暂时离开，
if you just backed off for a while,okay?
这真的能帮助我们的婚姻
No.
那不行
Huh?
什么?
I said no.
我说不行
I know what you said.I'm wondering why you said it.
我知道你在说什么 我想知道为什么你要说这些
Carlos isa diamond in the rough,
Carlos就像一颗
a flawed man to be sure,
有瑕疵的天然金刚石
but someone who is desperately searching
他拼命地找可以
for something to believe in.
寄托与信服的东西
To satisfy your materialism, he ended up breaking the law.
他最终触犯了法律只为了满足你对物质的需求
To deal with your adultery,he resorted to assault.
他打了别人只因为你搞通奸
As long as he's with you,
只要和你在一起
he will never find what he's looking for.
他就找不到他要寻的路
Well,I guess he should have thought of that
是嘛，那我倒觉得他应该在
before he married me.
娶我之前就要考虑好这些问题
Some marriagesare meant to be annulled.
有些婚姻需要解除的
What the hell kind of nunare you?
有你这样的修女？！
Look,if you try to comebetween me and my husband,
你要是想干涉我和我丈夫
I will take you down.
我可要找你麻烦
I grew up onthe south side of chicago.
我从芝加哥南部长大的
If you wanna threaten me,
如果你想威胁我
you're gonna have to doa lot better than that.
你要做得更好才是
You listen to me,you little bitch.
听我说，你这个小婊子
You do not want to start a war with me.
你不要和我对着干
well,I have god on my side.
可上帝是站我这边的
Bring it on.
你尽管来好了
you called for a bellman?
请问是您叫了服务员吗？
There's a charity dinnertaking place downstairs.
楼下正在开慈善宴会
My friend bree van de kampis one of the co-chairs.
我的朋友 Bree Van de Kamp 是其中的主办方
Give her this noteand walk away.
把这张便条给她然后马上走开
If she comes upin the elevator,call me.
如果看到她上了电梯，打电话给我
You think you can do that?
能做到吗?
Yes,sir.
当然，先生
- Excuse me,ma'am?
- 不好意思，夫人
Yes
有什么事吗?
I was asked to give this to you.
有人让我把这个给你
Oh,thank you.
哦，谢谢你
Barton.
Hello,detective barton.This is bree van de kamp.
你好，Barton 侦探 我是 Bree Van de Kamp
I need to talk to you about george williams.
我想跟你说说George Williams 的事情
Yeah,I was just gettingready to call you, mrs. Van de kamp.
哦，我正要想打给你，Van de Kamp 夫人
My men are at his house right now,
我部下正在他家里
and they've uncovered evidence that suggests
他们有证据说明
mr. Williams was responsible for your husband's death.
Williams 先生与你先生的死有关
- What? - Yeah,we found
- 什么？
rex's prescription bottles
- 是的，我们发现了Rex
and doctored potassium pills
吃的药瓶还有药用的钾吸收片
as well as some disturbing diary entries.
还有一些关于这些的日记
Mrs. Van de kamp?
Van de Kamp夫人？
Hello,sir.
你好，先生
Yes.She's,uh,on her way up.
是的，她上电梯了
Thank you very much.
非常感谢你
She loves me.
她爱我
She loves me not.
她不爱我
She loves me.
她爱我
she loves me not.
她不爱我
She loves me.
她爱我
operator,
接线员
this is a bit embarrassing, but I've...
很不好意思，
I've swallowed some pillsby mistake.
但是我好像吞错药了
I think you need to callan ambulance.
可不可以叫辆救护车
uh,uh,uh,they were--
嗯...吞了
they were just vitamins
哦，维生素片
see? False alarm.I'm fine.
哦，弄错了，我很好
Door's open.
门是开着的
Hey.
嘿
What were you thinking,taking the pills?
你都在想些什么 吃了这些安眠药?
I didn't hurt dr. Goldfine.
我没有伤害Goldfine医生
And for you to...
还有就是对你来说...
think me capable of...
认为我能够有能力...
that sort of...
做出那样的...
violence...
暴行...
george.
George.
I'm sorry.It's the pills.
对不起 是安眠药
Why are you telling me this?
为什么要告诉我这些?
Because maybe I don't have to die.
因为我或许并不应该死
I could face the police
我能够面对警察的
knowing that youwould be there for me...
特别是知道你会支持我...
that you'd stay my friend.
还会做我的朋友
Then I'll have somethingto live for.
那样我就会有继续活下去的理由
And then we'll call an ambulance and they'll pump your stomach.
那么我们会给你叫个救护车 让他们给你洗胃
Yes.
好的
I want to help you,
我想要帮你
but in order to do that, I need to forgive you, and...
但是为了能作到这一点 我先要原谅你, 不过...
I can't do that until you admit what you've done.
除非你承认那些你干了的事情 我做不到
I didn't push goldfine.
我没有推goldfine
Yes,you did.
不，你干了
But that's not what I'm talking about.
但是那不是我想说的
You killed rex.
你杀了rex
But I know it wasn't totally your fault
但是我知道那不都是你的错
because you're not well.
因为我知道你那时不正常
So if you'll just be honest with me,
所以，如果你对我说实话
I can forgive you.
我会原谅你的
It'll be the hardest thing I've ever done,
这将是我这辈子做的最困难的事情
but I'll do it.
但是我会做到的
But you have to--you have to tell me the truth.
但是你必须--你必须告诉我真相
look,I'm in trouble here.
你瞧,我这里有点麻烦
We need to call someone.
我们需要打电话
Not until you admit what you've done.
你先要承认所干的事情
I love you.
我爱你
Anything I may have done,I did for you.
不管我做了什么,都是为了你
Because you wanted me to.
因为，你想要我去干
You know you did.
你知道你想的
we need to callthe ambulance.
我们必须叫救护车
I... called them while you were asleep.
我... 在你睡着了的时候已经打过了
They're already on their way.
他们应该已经在路上
It's not always that easy to distinguish
我们并不总是很轻易就能分清
the good guys from the bad guys.
好人和坏人的
Sinners can surprise you.
有罪的人会让你大吃一惊
And the same is true for saints.
圣人也会
Why do we try to define people as simply good or simply evil?
为什么我们要把人们简单的 分为纯粹的好人或者纯粹的魔鬼呢？
Because no one wants to admit that compassion and cruelty
因为没有人会愿意承认残暴和仁慈
can live side by side in one heart...
会存在于同一个身体里...
and that anyone is capable of anything.
也不会承认自己能干出任何事情